Guide to the ILR School Communications Department Photographs 1997-2002
ILR School Communications Department Photographs
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
ILR School Communications Department Photographs, 1997-2002
/4264 P
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR);; Communications Department
2.6 linear ft.
Photographs.
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Communications Department--Photographs; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations--Photographs
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Related Collections:
/4264: ILR School Communications Department Director's Files
/4264 PUBS: ILR School Communications Department Publications
CONTAINER LIST
- Slides (Box 1, Folder 1)
  23 slides
- CORE - 1998 Spring (Box 1, Folder 2)
  26 slides
- CORE - 1998 Spring (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 3)
  17 slides
- CORE - 1997 Fall (Box 1, Folder 4)
  32 slides
- CORE - 1997 Fall (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  11 slides
- OCS Fall 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- OCS Fall 1997 (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  19 slides
- OCS Fall 1997 (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 8)
  15 slides
- OCS Fall 1997 (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  31 slides
- CORE 1997 Spring (Box 1, Folder 10)
  22 slides
- CORE 1997 Spring (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  20 slides
- CORE 1997 Spring (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- CORE 1997 Spring (cont.) (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Slides (Box 1, Folder 14)
  27 slides
- Clock Tower photographs (Box 1, Folder 15)
  3 color photographs
- Nancy Lampen, Susan Brecher (Box 1, Folder 16)
  2 color photographs, 2 black and white
- Contact sheets (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Karen Schoessow (Box 1, Folder 18)
  2 photographs
- Mary Riley (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Mary Lee Bombay, Luke farmer (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Mike Goodman, Sherrie Morales, Susan Brecher (Box 1, Folder 21)
  3 photographs
- Mike Goodman, Thomas Quimby, Anthony Panos, Kathy Devine, Pam Henderson, Karen Roman (Box 1, Folder 22)
  16 photographs
- Chronicle - issue v.33, no. 22, February 14, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  newspaper
- Die EventFotografen / Robert Hausmann@Stefan Zeitz -- Projekt: CAHRS Spring Sponsor Meeting 2002, Germany Berlin, 03, June (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Film no. 1555/00 - 11/17/00 - C -- Barry DeLibero - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Film no. 1555/00 - 11/17/00 - B -- Barry DeLibero - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Film no. 1555/00 - 11/17/00 - A -- Barry DeLibero - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Ithaca - IHREDP -- 9/28-10/3/1997 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - F -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - E -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - D -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - C -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - B -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Film no. 1554/00 - 11/16/00 - A -- Frank DiMeo - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - F -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - E -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Photo print numbering and guide information (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Film no. 571/01 - 05/10/01 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - F -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - E -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Film no. 657/00 - 5/19/00 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Film no. 641/00 - 5/18/00 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Film no. 641/00 - 5/18/00 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Film no. 641/00 - 5/18/00 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Film no. 641/00 - 5/18/00 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Spring Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Film # 467/98 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Film no. 1053/00 - 8/22/00 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Roundtable Sessions - Statler Hotel (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 19)
- National Academy of Human Resources Ceremony - 11/4/1999 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Contact sheets and negatives (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Pucik, Vladimir (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Meeting - All Speakers (Box 5, Folder 5)
- CAHRS (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Ford Motor Company (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Misc. (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Misc. Cornell University Photography (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Portraits (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Tony (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Film no. 11/13/03 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Film no. 1555/00 - 11/17/00 - D -- Barry DeLibero - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Film no. 571/01 - 05/10/01 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - F -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - E -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Film no. 870/01 - 08/28/01 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Executive Roundtable - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Film no. 579/01 - 05/11/01 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Film no. 579/01 - 05/11/01 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Film no. 579/01 - 05/11/01 - B -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Film no. 579/01 - 05/11/01 - A -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Film no. 571/01 - 05/10/01 - D -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Film no. 571/01 - 05/10/01 - C -- Charles Harrington - CAHRS Fall Sponsor Meeting - Statler Hotel (Box 4, Folder 7)
- CAHRS - Int'l. Spring Sponsor Meeting (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Film no. 826/03 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Conference Photos and Negatives (Box 5, Folder 20)
- National Academy of Human Resources Program (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Dyer, Lee (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Singapore brochure '96; Human Resource (printer); Broch Teamoff [4 floppy discs] (Box 5, Folder 17)
- KL98 -- 2/16-20/98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Singapore HREDP 3/17-21/97, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Shanghai - Reception Photos from Thomas Tsui - 5/13/98, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Ithaca 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Human Resource Exec. Dev. Program, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Singapore 96? (Box 5, Folder 11)
- #930685 -- PGP ILR (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Contact sheets and negatives (Box 6, Folder 1)